Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Negatives, 1880s-1986 and undated, (11 boxes)
  - Officers and Staff--Large Format
    - Brownell, C.A. (1st Agent, JWT Detroit), 1910s (Box NE4)
    - Brundage, Howard, 1962-1970, (2 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Bullmore, Jeremy, circa 1970s-1981, (2 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Carlton, William Jones, circa 1877 (Box NE4)
    - Carroll, Carroll, circa 1966 (Box NE4)
    - Cherington, Paul T., 1930s, (2 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Colwell, Robert Bob (by Karsh), undated, (2 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Connell, Hugh P., 1965 and undated, (3 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Cronin, Margaret, undated (Box NE4)
    - Curry, Ellen, 1976 (Box NE4)
    - Denton, Kelsey, 1953 (Box NE4)
    - Dilbert, George C., early 1960s (Box NE4)
    - Dorun, Luchinda, undated (Box NE4)
    - Doyer, Robert, 1968 (Box NE4)
    - Effer, Gordon, 1971 (Box NE4)
    - Elton, Wallace, undated, (8 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Elton, Wallace W. (in group including Normal Rockwell bow tie), undated (Box NE4)
    - Emory, Richard, 1965 (Box NE4)
    - Erskine, William H., circa 1963 (Box NE4)
    - Fairington, Alan, undated (Box NE4)
    - Fickinger, Wayne, 1967 (Box NE4)
    - Fickinger, Wayne (TV on hoc), undated (Box NE4)
    - Fielden, E.J. Peter, undated, (2 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Flower, Henry, circa 1930-1950s, (3 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Fortinberry, Glen, undated (Box NE4)
    - Foster, Anne, 1967 (Box NE4)
    - Fragasso, Ray, undated (Box NE4)
    - Gene, Secunda (Fireman), undated (Box NE4)
    - Gill, Michael, undated (Box NE4)
    - Glah, Roy (Amsterdam Office Manager), Doyer, Robert (Benelux Manager), circa 1967 (Box NE4)
    - Glymm, Thomas, 1971 (Box NE4)
    - Gorman, Frank, undated (Box NE4)
    - Grady, Elwood, undated (Box NE4)
    - Gross, Michael, undated (Box NE4)
    - Gunn, Alexander H., undated (Box NE4)
    - Hackett, Byron, undated (Box NE4)
    - Handley, Harold, 1962 (Box NE4)
    - Hardy, Thelma, circa 1965 (Box NE4)
    - Henderson, Howard, 1934 (Box NE4)
    - Hinks, Kennett, circa 1929-1960s, (4 folders) (Box NE4)
    - Hunna, Greg, undated (Box NE4)
    - Hurd, Richard, undated (Box NE4)
    - James, David, undated (Box NE5)
    - Johnson, Frank, 1960s (Box NE5)
    - Johnston, Arno, 1930s-1940s, (2 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Johnston, Donald G., 1960s-1981, (23 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Johnston, Donald G. and family, circa 1955 (Box NE5)
    - Johnston, Donald Director badge, 1981 (Box NE5)
    - Jones, Alun, undated (Box NE5)
    - Keane, John G., 1968 (Box NE5)
    - Kennedy, James W. (Jim), undated (Box NE5)
    - Kennedy, James W. (Jim), undated (Box NE5)
    - King, Margaret (Peggy), undated (Box NE5)
    - Kinney, Gilbert, undated, (2 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Kover, Arthur, undated (Box NE5)
    - Kovas, Ron, circa 1979 (Box NE5)
    - Lanigan, Denis, circa 1961-1967 and undated, (5 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Laurie, William D., circa 1964 and undated, (2 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Lee, Henry A., circa 1955, (2 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Lehner, Paul, 1964 (Box NE5)
    - Luisi, Marie, 1970s (Box NE5)
    - Mackey, Peter, circa 1995 (Box NE5)
    - Manning, Burt, 1966-1990 (Box NE5)
    - Manning, Burt, 1969 (Box NE5)
    - Marans, David, 1990s (Box NE5)
    - Martell, Charles, 1966 (Box NE5)
    - McMahon, Doug, 1990s (Box NE5)
    - McQuigg, John, 1969 (Box NE5)
    - Meads, Walter Chip, circa 1964 (Box NE5)
    - Meek, Sam, undated (Box NE5)
    - Meek, Samuel 1920s-1950s and undated, (12 folders) (Box NE5)
    - Meek, Sam (at Annual JWT/BMRB Ball at Governor's House London), 1957 (Box NE5)
    - Meek, Samuel (with wife, plane in New Delhi), 1956 (Box NE5)
    - Meek, Samuel (with wife alighting from plane art New Delhi airport, undated (Box NE5)
    - Milliken, Cynthia, undated (Box NE6)
    - Milliken, Cynthia, undated (Box NE6)
    - Modisell, John, 1966 (Box NE6)
    - Monsarrat, John, 1963, (2 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Muller, Jan, 1973-1974 (Box NE6)
    - Mygatt, Philip, 1966 July (Box NE6)
    - O'Brien, Patrick E., 1967 (Box NE6)
    - O'Brien, Walter, 1979 and undated, (2 folders) (Box NE6)
    - O'Dell, Norman, circa 1965 (Box NE6)
    - O'Donnell, William S., 1967 (Box NE6)
    - O'Grady, Thomas F., undated (Box NE6)
    - Olshan, Larry, circa1980 (Box NE6)
    - Olsen, Sidney, circa 1956 (Box NE6)
    - Palen, Gilbert, 1964 (Box NE6)
    - Palmer, William G., undated (Box NE6)
    - Parker, Joan, undated (Box NE6)
    - Patterson, Jim, undated (Box NE6)
    - Peirce, Evelyn, undated (Box NE6)
    - Pierce, Thurman, undated (Box NE6)
    - Raymond, Charles, 1900s and undated, (2 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Reeves, George (Karsh photograph), undated (Box NE6)
    - Reeves, George C., undated (Box NE6)
    - Resor, Helen Landsdowne, 1917-1920s and undated, (4 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Resor, Helen Landsdowne (Steichen photograph), undated (Box NE6)
    - Resor, Stanley, 1921-1955, (4 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Resor, Stanley Cattleboat Resor, undated (Box NE6)
    - Ross, William E., undated, (2 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Rydholm, Ralph, undated (Box NE6)
    - Sanderson, Jean, 1951 (Box NE6)
    - Sanderson, Jean (Mrs. Denis Lanigan), 1951 (Box NE6)
    - Sanderson, Jean (R.), Campbell-Harris, D. (L.), 1951 (Box NE6)
    - Schweitzer, Peter, 1998 (Box NE6)
    - Scollay, Jack, undated (Box NE6)
    - Senior, Raimond, undated (Box NE6)
    - Seymour, Dan, 1940s-1983 and undated, (7 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Sharman, John, circa 1983, (2 folders) (Box NE6)
    - Sherman, Ron, undated (Box NE7)
    - Simonson, Carl W., undated (Box NE7)
    - Spivak, Helayne, undated (Box NE7)
    - Stanton, Henry, 1940s (Box NE7)
    - Stephenson, Nancy, undated (Box NE7)
    - Stevens, Henry M., 1950 (Box NE7)
    - Strouse, Norman, 1920s-1970s and undated, (17 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Sutton, Thomas, 1960s-1970s and undated, (5 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter (in chair), undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter, Tyler portrait, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter & Walter Roosevelt Thompson, circa 1892 (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter W. Roosevelt Thompson his son, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter 1885 (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter, The Stella, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter (Tyler Portrait), undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter (portrait), undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter and family, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter with W. Roosevelt Thompson, his son, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter, circa 1880 (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter & Thompson, Margaret Roggs Bogle, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter as a boy, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter with mother, undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter (Tyler Portrait), undated (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, James Walter (seated in ornate chair), 1915 (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, Margaret Riggs Boyle (Mrs.), 1887 (Box NE7)
    - Thompson, Mrs. Margaret and Cornelia Boyle, undated (Box NE7)
    - Treasure, John, undated (Box NE7)
    - Trzuskowski, John, 1980 (Box NE7)
    - Van Etten, Floyd, 1965 (Box NE7)
    - Walter, undated (Box NE7)
    - Walthius, George, 1972 (Box NE7)
    - Ward, Kenneth, undated (Box NE7)
    - Wason, Thomas, 1960s (Box NE7)
    - Watson, Art, 1963-1970s (Box NE7)
    - Webster, Juan (Jack) G.O., 1963 and undated, (6 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Weith, Warren, undated (Box NE7)
    - Welty, Robert, 1960 (Box NE7)
    - White, Robert F., undated (Box NE7)
    - Wilson, Edward B. (Ted), undated, (2 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Wilson, Edward G., 1930-1965 and undated, (6 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Wohl, Jack, undated (Box NE7)
    - Yalowitz, Ed, 1965 (Box NE7)
    - Young, James Webb, 1940s-1960s, (6 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Yuspeh, Sonia E., 1981, (4 folders) (Box NE7)
    - Zarry, Peter T., undated (Box NE7)
    - Photocopies of notes that came with pictures of Michael Cooper-Evans & Allen Thomas, 1989 (Box NE7)
    - Photocopy of note that came with pictures of Dominique Simonin, R.Burns, W.L. Preschel, A.Farmington, C.Jones, 1989 (Box NE7)
  - Offices--Large Format
    - Corporate
      - Art work--Epstein, Joseph, undated (Box NE8)
      - Art work--Prendergast, Maurice, undated (Box NE8)
      - Art work--Senior, Rai, undated (Box NE8)
      - Artifact--Letter from J. Walter Thompson, 1893 (Box NE8)
      - Artifact--T-Square, circa 1960 (Box NE8)
      - Event--Board of Directors Meeting, 1986 (Box NE8)
      - Event--Commodore's Club, Spain, 1994 (Box NE8)
      - Event--First Executive Session of 4-A's, 1917 (Box NE8)
      - Event--Retirement party for Stanley Resor, 1961 (Box NE8)
    - New York Office
      - Buildings
        - 38 Park Row--Exterior, 1989 (Box NE8)
        - 41 Park Row--Exterior, 1891 (Box NE8)
        - 44-60 East Twenty-Third Street, 1905 (Box NE8)
        - 244 Madison Avenue
          - A corner of the Pictorial Department, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - A portion of the library in the Research Department, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Colonial Dining Room, 1923 (Box NE8)
          - Exterior, 1917 (Box NE8)
          - Interior Views, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Office Views, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Reception Room, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Section of files for 190,000 newspapers and 26,000 other publications, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Sorting newspapers and magazines for files-ten clerks constantly on duty, 1918 (Box NE8)
          - Test Kitchen, circa 1924 (Box NE8)
          - The Studio where artists sketch the design on which finished advertisements are constructed, 1918 (Box NE8)
        - 380 Hudson Street (Survey) Warehouse, 1983 (Box NE8)
        - 466 Lexington Avenue
          - Executive Office, undated (Box NE8)
          - Exterior, 1970s (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Archives, 1980-1986 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1981 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Mock-up, 1981 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Office--Art Director Mock-up, 1981 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Office--Johnston, Don, 1986 (Box NE8)
        - 1500 Broadway- Entertainment Group New Building, undated (Box NE8)
        - Graybar Building
          - Exterior, 1927-1980s (Box NE8)
          - Exterior, 1980 (Box NE8)
          - Interior, undated (Box NE8)
          - Interior, 1929 (Box NE8)
          - Interior, 1963 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1923 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Colonial Dining Room, 1923 (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Research Kitchen, 1920s (Box NE8)
          - Interior--Yellin's History of Printing, 1929 (Box NE8)
          - Grille work, undated (Box NE8)
          - Lecture Hall, 1930s (Box NE8)
          - Michael's Pillar, 1971 (Box NE8)
          - Offices--Group Head Women's Copy, 1920s (Box NE8)
          - Offices--Meek, Samuel W, 1947 (Box NE8)
          - Reception Area, 1929 (Box NE8)
          - Reception Area, 1940s (Box NE8)
          - Reception Area, 1945 (Box NE8)
          - Reception Area; Lippold Sculpture, 1960s (Box NE8)
          - Floor plan, 1947 (Box NE8)
          - NYC JWT Office-Entrance from elevator to Reception room, undated (Box NE8)
      - Clients
        - Andrew Jergens, undated (Box NE8)
        - Anthracite Institute, 1945-1946 (Box NE8)
        - Blue Cross, 1954 (Box NE8)
        - Chesebrough-Pond's, undated (Box NE8)
        - Eastman Kodak1954-56 (Box NE8)
        - Eastman Kodak, undated (Box NE8)
        - Eastman Kodak--Billboards, 1970s (Box NE8)
        - Ford Television, 1950s (Box NE8)
        - Ford Advertisement, 1945 (Box NE8)
        - Garrett Flight Systems, 1967 (Box NE8)
        - Gorey Display, undated (Box NE8)
        - JWT House advertisements, 1916-1941 (Box NE8)
        - Lever Brothers--Lux Video Theatre, 1955 Apr (Box NE8)
        - Libby-McNeil, corned beef, 1930 (Box NE8)
        - Maxwell Coffee, undated (Box NE8)
        - Odorono, 1919 (Box NE8)
        - Oscar Mayer, undated (Box NE8)
        - Pan Am, 1950s-1960s (Box NE8)
        - Shell--City of Tomorrow, 1937 (Box NE9)
        - Simmons Mattress Commercial, 1974 (Box NE9)
        - Standard Brands, H.V. Kaltern born. Edits the News Radio-TV Department, mid 1950s (Box NE9)
        - Toys 'R' Us, 1982 (Box NE9)
        - Competitive advertisements (Jello, D-Zerta, Tang), 1966-1969 (Box NE9)
      - Events
        - Athletic Teams--Basketball Team, undated (Box NE9)
        - Crucifer on Broadway, undated (Box NE9)
        - Crucifer of Blood on location Grand Central, undated (Box NE9)
        - Financial Managers Cocktail Party, undated (Box NE9)
        - Financial Managers Meeting, undated (Box NE9)
        - New Opening, undated (Box NE9)
        - SMTPE, undated (Box NE9)
        - Sven Mohr Party, undated (Box NE9)
        - The Wiz Poster, undated (Box NE9)
        - United Fund Meeting, undated (Box NE9)
      - Group portraits
        - Athletic Teams--Women's softball team, 1968 (Box NE9)
        - Amtrack Group, undated (Box NE9)
        - Christmas Chorus, undated (Box NE9)
        - Ford Pick Up T-Shirt Girls, undated (Box NE9)
        - New Arrival Group, undated (Box NE9)
        - The Boys from Brazil, undated (Box NE9)
        - United Fund Group, undated (Box NE9)
      - Model/Celebrity photographs
        - Oneida, Cathy, with Bob Crosby, undated (Box NE9)
      - Radio-TV Department, 1950s (Box NE9)
    - Chicago Office
      - Buildings
        - French/Provincial Dining Room, 1930s (Box NE9)
        - Lytton Building, 1918, 1940s (Box NE9)
        - Offices--Blair, M.J., 1930s (Box NE9)
        - Offices--Staunton, Henry T., 1930s (Box NE9)
        - Offices--Stocklin, Walter, 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Offices--Woolf, J.D., 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Reception Area, 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Research Kitchen, circa 1919 (Box NE9)
        - Research Kitchen, 1919 (Box NE9)
        - Rookery Building, 1940s (Box NE9)
        - Spanish Kitchen, 1931 Sept. 1 (Box NE9)
        - Tacoma Building, 1918 (Box NE9)
        - View of reception Room, 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Wrigley Building, 1920-1950s (Box NE9)
        - Wrigley Building, 1920-1950s (Box NE9)
      - Clients--Kraft, mid 1950s (Box NE9)
      - Departments
        - Art Department, 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Art Department, 1931 (Box NE9)
        - Mechanical Department, 1931 Sept. 1 (Box NE9)
        - Media Department, 1937 Sept. 1 (Box NE9)
        - Research Department, 1931 Sept. 1 (Box NE9)
        - Traffic Department, 1931 Sept. 1 (Box NE9)
        - Traffic Department, with time-scheduling board in background, 1931 (Box NE9)
      - Events
        - Ad Age--Advertising Week, circa 1976 (Box NE9)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box NE9)
      - Group portraits
        - Chicago Office Executives, 1934 (Box NE9)
        - Director of Home Economics, Women Creative Vice Presidents, undated (Box NE9)
        - Male Staff, 1902 (Box NE9)
        - Women Executives, 1959 (Box NE9)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box NE9)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box NE9)
      - Other images
        - Advertisement, undated (Box NE9)
        - House advertisement, undated (Box NE9)
        - Proclamation, 1989 (Box NE9)
    - Other U.S. Offices
      - Boston (Box NE10)
        - Boston Safe Deposit and Trust Company, 1918 (Box NE10)
      - Cincinnati
        - Buildings--First National Bank Building, 1918 (Box NE10)
        - Clients--Jergens, 1920 (Box NE10)
        - Group Portraits--V.C. Ward, George C. Reeves, Howard Henderson, Edward J. Burke, circa 1940s (Box NE10)
      - Detroit
        - Buildings--Kresge Building, 1918 (Box NE10)
        - Clients--Ford, undated (Box NE10)
        - Clients--Ford Trucks, 1961-1964 (Box NE10)
        - Events--Stag Day, 1952 (Box NE10)
        - Group Portraits--Office Staff, 1953 (Box NE10)
      - San Francisco
        - Clients--Kilpatrick's Bakeries Billboard, circa 1968 (Box NE10)
        - Clients--Sprint, undated (Box NE10)
        - Group Portraits--Staff Meeting, 1936 May (Box NE10)
        - Unidentified, undated (Box NE10)
    - International Offices
      - Australia--Sydney
        - Buildings--Interior, undated (Box NE10)
        - Group Portrait-Sydney Staff, 1933 (Box NE10)
      - Brazil
        - Clients--Giroflex, undated (Box NE10)
        - Clients--Topper, undated (Box NE10)
        - Events--International Festival of Advertising Films, undated (Box NE10)
      - Canada--Montreal
        - Buildings--1600 Dorchester Blvd. West, Northern Building, 1964 (Box NE10)
      - Denmark--Copenhagen
        - Group Portrait--Managing Director Bjorn Obro's Home, undated (Box NE10)
      - England--London
        - Buildings--Bush House, 1964 (Box NE10)
        - Buildings--Bush House, 1930s (Box NE10)
        - Buildings--Bush House, 1930s (Box NE10)
        - Buildings--Bush House Radio Department, 1930s (Box NE10)
        - Events--Annual JWT Ball, 1937 Jan. (Box NE10)
        - Events--Flags at half-staff for death, 1981 Aug. 16 (Box NE10)
      - Germany--Frankfurt
        - Buildings--Bockenheimer Landstrasse 104, 1961 (Box NE10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box NE10)
      - Greece--Athens
        - Clients- Delta SA negatives of Chicago Ice Cream, 1984 (Box NE10)
      - India--Bombay
        - Group Portraits- Staff, 1930 (Box NE10)
      - Italy--Milan
        - Buildings, undated (Box NE10)
      - Japan--Tokyo
        - Buildings--Akasauka Denmacho, 1964 Sept. (Box NE10)
      - Netherlands (Holland)--Amsterdam
        - Events--Office Move, 1969 Aug. (Box NE10)
        - Buildings--Exterior, 1956 (Box NE10)
      - Sweden--Stockholm
        - Client--Nestle, 1984 (Box NE10)
        - Kungagatan, 1930 (Box NE10)
  - Officers and Staff--Oversize
    - Reber, John U., circa 1930s (Box NE11)
- Pond's Photographs and Negatives, circa 1927-1954 and undated [RESTRICTED], (28 boxes)
  Includes images primarily of celebrities and noted socialites, taken for a long-running campaign for Chesebrough-Pond's beauty products. Arranged into two categories: Photographs and Negatives. Photographs reside in numbered folders. Negatives are sorted by format and arranged according to the corresponding folder number; loose negatives are arranged alphabetically by name.
  Restrictions on Access: Reproduction-quality copies of Pond's Advertising Photographs may not be produced for non-JWT users.
  - Large Format Photographs
    - P1-1. Betty, Lady Russell of Liverpool. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-2. Duke, Mrs. Anthony Drexel. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO1)
    - P1-3. Elizabeth, Duchess of York (later Queen Elizabeth)--Clippings. Photographer: Unknown, 1928 (Box PO1)
    - P1-4. Elizabeth, Duchess of York (later Queen Elizabeth)--Correspondence. Photographer: Unknown, 1928 (Box PO1)
    - P1-5. Eulalia, Princess of Spain. Photographer: Mouls, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-6. Eulalia, Princess of Spain. Photographer: Vandyk, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-7. Hill, Lady Anne. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-8. King-Tenison, Lady Brigid. Photographer: Wildman, Shaw, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-9. LaFalaise, Countess de. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO1)
    - P1-10. LaPrade, Evelyn Byrd (Mrs. O. H. Lorentzen II). Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO1)
    - P1-11. LaPrade, Evelyn Byrd (Mrs. O. H. Lorentzen II). Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO1)
    - P2-1. Loch, Lady. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO2)
    - P2-2. Louden, Lady Prudence. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO2)
    - P2-3. Lubersac, Countess de. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, 1945 (Box PO2)
    - P2-4. Lubersac, Countess de. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, 1945 (Box PO2)
    - P2-5. McAdoo, Cynthia. Photographer: Greene, undated (Box PO2)
    - P2-6. McAdoo, Cynthia. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO2)
    - P2-7. McAdoo, Cynthia. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, circa 1946 (Box PO2)
    - P2-8. McCormick, Mrs. Alister. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO2)
    - P2-9. McCormick, Constance. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO2)
    - P3-1. McCormick, Mrs. David. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO3)
    - P3-2. McCormick, Mrs. Michael H. Photographer: Hiltz (?), 1954 (Box PO3)
    - P3-3. McCormick, Mrs. Michael H. Photographer: Hiltz (?), 1954 (Box PO3)
    - P3-4. McCormick, Mrs. Michael H. Photographer: Hiltz (?), 1954 (Box PO3)
    - P3-5. Mary, Countess of Howe. Photographer: Cecil, Hugh, undated (Box PO3)
    - P3-6. Mary, Countess of Howe. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO3)
    - P3-7. Mason, Mrs. George Grant (nee Jane Kendall). Photographer: Underwood, 1926 (Box PO3)
    - P3-8. Matthews, Mrs. Agnes De Saint Phalle. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1949 (Box PO3)
    - P3-9. Matthews, Mrs. Agnes De Saint Phalle. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1949 (Box PO3)
    - P3-10. Matthews, Mrs. Agnes De Saint Phalle. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1949 (Box PO3)
    - P4-1. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO4)
    - P4-2. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO4)
    - P4-3. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO4)
    - P4-4. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO4)
    - P4-5. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1950 (Box PO4)
    - P4-6. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1952 (Box PO4)
    - P4-7. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1953 (Box PO4)
    - P4-8. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1954 (Box PO4)
    - P4-9. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1954 (Box PO4)
    - P4-10. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1954 (Box PO4)
    - P4-11. Milford-Haven, Romaine, Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1954 (Box PO4)
    - P5-1. Morgan, Camilla. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO5)
    - P5-2. Mountbatten, Lady Louis. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO5)
    - P5-3. Mountbatten, Lady Louis. Photographer: Unknown, undated (Box PO5)
    - P5-4. Mountbatten, Lady Louis (Her vanity table). Photographer: Cecil, Hugh, undated (Box PO5)
    - P5-5. Mountbatten, Lady Louis. Photographer: Wilding, Dorothy, circa 1927 (Box PO5)
    - P5-6. Nemours, Duchess de. Photographer: Rockwell, Stevens, undated (Box PO5)
    - P5-7. Newcastle, Duchess of. Photographer: Parkinson, 1954 (Box PO5)
    - P5-8. Normanton, Countess of. Photographer: Wildman, Shaw, undated (Box PO5)
    - P6-1. Pell, Mrs. John. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO6)
    - P6-2. Petitville, Countess. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO6)
    - P6-3. Petitville, Countess. Photographer: Halsman, Philippe, undated (Box PO6)
    - P6-4. Queensberry, the Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1949 (Box PO6)
    - P6-5. Queensberry, the Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1953 (Box PO6)
    - P6-6. Queensberry, the Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1953 (Box PO6)
    - P6-7. Queensberry, the Marchioness of. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1953 (Box PO6)
    - P6-8. Radnor, Countess of. Photographer: Unknown, 1942 (Box PO6)
    - P6-9. Rafaelle, Duchess of Leinster. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1948 (Box PO6)
    - P6-10. Rafaelle, Duchess of Leinster. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1948 (Box PO6)
    - P7-1. Reed, Lady Penelope. Photographer: Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1953 (Box PO7)